Earth is a memory worth fighting for.
Oblivion is a action, science fiction, adventure
film directed by Joseph Kosinski.
Jack Harper is one of the last few drone repairmen stationed on Earth.
Part of a massive operation to extract vital resources after decades of war with a
terrifying threat known as the Scavs, Jack’s mission is nearly complete.
His existence is brought crashing down when he rescues a
beautiful  stranger from a downed spacecraft.
Her arrival triggers a chain of events that  forces him to question
everything he knows and puts the fate of humanity in his hands.
Jack, played by Tom Cruise.
Beech, played by Morgan Freeman.
Julia, played by Olga Kurylenko.
Victoria, played by Andrea Riseborough.
Sykes, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Sally, played by Melissa Leo.
Oblivion is a 2013 American epic post-apocalyptic science fiction action film produced and directed by Joseph Kosinski from a screenplay by Karl Gajdusek and Michael deBruyn,
starring Tom Cruise in the main role alongside Morgan Freeman, Olga Kurylenko, Andrea Riseborough, Nikolaj Coster-Waldau, and Melissa Leo in supporting roles.
Based on Kosinski's unpublished Radical Comics graphic novel of the same name, the film pays homage to 1970s sci-fi, and is a "love story" set in 2077 on an Earth desolated by an alien war; a
maintenance technician on the verge of completing his mission finds a woman who survived from a space ship crash, leading him to question his purpose and discover the truth about the war.
Oblivion premiered in Buenos Aires on March 26, 2013, and was
released in theaters by Universal Pictures on April 19.
The film grossed $286 million worldwide on a production budget of
$120 million and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, dystopia,
post-apocalyptic future, based on comic, space.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.